http://miamivalley.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYMiami Valley Church recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use our services value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of information collected on miamivalley.org and live.miamivalley.org. We provide this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using Miami Valley Church web sites.Personal information and other data we collectMiami Valley Church collects personal information when you attend a worship service, register for an event, perform a donation or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other Miami Valley Church services to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.Miami Valley Church uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve the quality of our services.Miami Valley Church servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.UsesWe may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested, including services that display customized content.We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve Miami Valley Church technologies and services.When we use third parties to assist us in processing your information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing credit card or ACH fraud, preventing imminent harm or danger, and ensuring the security of our network and services.Any personal information that is collected as part of a financial transaction is shared with the beneficiaries of said transactions. For instance, if you register services from a third-party, that party will have access to the personal information that you shared (such as address, phone and email address).Your ChoicesWe offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible.You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.We will make good faith effort to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, whenever reasonably possible.
SECURITYPlease note that Miami Valley Church never stores security codes (e.g., CVV2), PINs and magnetic track data. We avoid storing sensitive information, but when we must it is encrypted using the same methods that major financial institutions and the military use. Access to this data is severely limited by a number of digital and physical protections, in line with PCI-DSS requirements.When you create your account, you will determine your own login id and password. If you forget your login id or password, you can have the system email it to you by entering the email address that you used when you created your account. If you need help or cannot remember the email address you used, you can contact us at finance@miamivalley.org. You can also change your password at any time.Please help us keep your information safe by protecting your login information. Access to sensitive personal and financial information can be gained by letting someone else use your account or by leaving the information for someone else to see. Miami Valley Church will never call you to ask for your login information.
Contact Us
40 S 5th St, Miamisburg, OH 45342
mymiamivalley@miamivalley.org
(937) 847-0757
Copyright 2020, Miami Valley Church. All Rights Reserved.
